Why at a time like this?!
My brother... Where is my brother?
We don't know anything.
All of you! Get down on the ground!
Raise both hands. All of you!
All of you don't move!
What do you want us...
Sorry for disturbing you.
おお おお おお おお おおおう
撃つてるねえ やつてるねえ
He's going at it, he's going at it!
ん? マシンガン?
それはそれで…
A machine gun?
Now that is interesting in its own right!
面白そうじやん!
ノ\ツ ノ\ツ ハツ…
何だつてんだよ 疆さんよお
What was that, sis?!
I didn't know it was going to turn out like this!
こんなの 聞いてねえぞ~
Dangerous...
ヤバい… ヤバい ヤバい
Dangerous, dangerous.
ヤバい ヤバい ヤバい
Dangerous...
Dangerous, dangerous.
ヤバい 何だよ 何が起こってんだよ
食堂車でよォ !
Dangerous...
What's going on in the dining car?!
Is he killing, is he getting killed?
殺せんの? 殺されんの?
どつちよ マジで
Which is it, seriously?!
Hey, hey, this is exciting!
オイオイ ドキ ドキするなあ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What do you mean?!
どういうことだつ!
As if it isn't bad enough already that our profit has been stolen,
アガリを奪ゎれただけならまだしも
you tell me to believe such a silly story?!
そんな与太話で俺を
ごまかせると思つてんのかつ !
Well it is the truth...
う それが事実なんで…
A pair of robbers wearing a Babe Ruth and a Ty Cobb uniform...
ベ一ブル一スと夕イ力ツブの
ユ二フオ一ムを着た2人組の強盗に…
力キ一ン!
That's impossible!
ありえね工!
Well... We asked the transporter responsible for this failure as well but...
それが… その不始末しでかした
運ぴ屋を尋問したんですが
どうやらウソではないようで…
It doesn't look like he's lying...
ふん! そのうえシダリスも
ドジつたつてのかい…
Are you tellin' me Sidalis screwed up too?!
Yes...
はい… 工場街の外れで…
At the edge of the factory grounds...
それが…
Well... He doesn't really look like a human anymore...
ほとんど人間の形を
とどめておりませんで…
たかカヾ こんな不良ごときに
By such a puny delinquent like him?!
You can't underestimate those people!
あの連中は あなどれません!
偵察に行ったほかの
We'd better tell the police—
もういい!
雑魚に手こずりぉっz
Enough!
Being held up by that small fry.
まずは その妙な強盗からだ
We're gonna deal with that strange robber duo first.
Let's put the heat on each and every couple in the city!
街中の力ッブ丿しという力ッブ丿しを
締め上げてやる!
やめろよォ 叔父貴ィ
んなことしたら
Don't do it, uncle!
People will think it's the inferiority complex of an unpopular old man.
もてないジジイの
ひがみだと思われちまうぜ
はあ… ラツ ド!
今は貴様の相手をしている暇はない
Ladd!
I don't have time to deal with you now!
とつとと うせろ!
Get out of here!
あれあれあれ? 何冷たいこと
言っちゃってんだよ 叔父貴ィ
Now, now...
What harsh things are you saying now, uncle...
The only thing you care for less than your life: money,
あんたの命の次に大事な金が
人様にぷんどられちまったんだろ?
has been plundered from you by other people, right?
That's why I came by with some good news.
だから俺力ヾいい二ユ一スを
持つてきてやつたつつ一のによ
貴様のいい二ユ一スなど
聞く耳持たん
I don't want to listen to the 'good' news you bring!
Even if you say so...
そうは言つてもよう
どうせ叔父貴のやることなんざ
What you plan to do anyway...
Making a very thorough search for the criminals,
犯人を草の根分けても捜し出して
and then choking them, choking them, choking them, choking them, choking them!
その首を絞め上げて
絞め上げて 絞め上げて
泡吹いても まだ絞め上げて
絞め上げて…
Even if they start to foam, choking them, choking them!
目ン玉 飛ぴ出しそうになっても
まだまだ絞め上げてえええ…
Even when their eyes look like they're going to pop out, still, still choking them...
And then...
で あげくにい
In the end...
ううつ!
ハイ さようなら…
てか?
"Yes, farewell!" it is.
Ladd...
ラツ ド… この殺人狂が…
You crazy murderer...
You sure say shameful things...
人聞きの悪いこと言つてくれるねえ
To the best assassin the Russo family has, me.
丿しツソファミリ一きつての
殺し屋の俺に向かって
殺し屋以外に
使い道がないからだろうカヾ!
That's because you have no other uses but being an assassin!
そんな俺様に頼るしかない自分ってのを
者えたことあるかい 叔父貴ィ
You ever thought about the fact that you can only count on me, uncle?
Listen up now.
いいかい あれだ
タ方にシ力ゴユ二オンから出る
特別急行
Tonight a special express train departs from Chicago,
it was called the Flying Pussyfoot I think.
フライングブツシ一フツ 卜って
言つたつけ?
The one that goes directly to New York without making any stops.
二壬一ヨ一クまでノンス卜ツプで
直行するやつ
I'll ride on that for a while,
あれをちよつと乗つ取つてさあ
マンハツ夕ンの街中に
突つ込ませてみようと思うんだぁ
and I'm thinking to crash the thing right into the middle of Manhattan.
But that's a bluff.
て言うのはブラフでよォ
まずそれで脅すだろぉ
That's just to intimidate them a bit first.
それで金払ゎなかつたら
And if they don't pay up then, we'll turn it into a kidnapping accident involving all the passengers.
乗客の誘拐事件に
即 切り替えってわけよ
That's true, isn't it?
まあ その 何だ 乗客の半分も殺せば
If we kill half the passengers, I think the railway company will pay us a nice amount.
鉄道会社は
金を払つてくれると思うんだぁ
人は殺せるし 金は手に入るし
いい者えだろ?
I get to kill some people and we get to make some money.
It's a good idea, don't you think?
ナ ノ
dあ 叔X貢イ?
Well, uncle?
出ていけ !
LEAVE!
おL! 誰かこいつを
つまみ出せ!
Hey, someone throw this guy out!
ハイ ハ一イ
Yes, yes.
ん? 何者だ?
Who are you?
They're my subordinates, my friends who have the same hobby as me.
俺の部下兼同じ趣味のお友達…
Oh by the way, this woman is Lua...
おっ ちなみにこの女はル一ア
俺の恋人兼彼女兼婚約者だから
よろしくな 叔父貴ィ
She's my lover, girlfriend and fiancée so... counting on your patronage, uncle.
Ah, yes, Sir...
あ あの どうも‥
ちよこつ と気が弱いつてやつ ?
She's really quiet...
But that's what brings down my high tension.
まあ そこがさ 俺のこのハイ な
テンシヨンと中和されて…
Shut up, stupid brat!
黙れ このクソガキ !
Understand this! You just go and kidnap and kill people!
いいか! 誘拐でも殺人でも
勝手にするがいい
However, I won't allow you to mention my name!
だが組の名を出すことは許さん !
どこの誰かも分からない人間として
勝手に殺して勝手に死ね…
As a complete John Doe you just go kill and die—
わ一つてるつて!
I understand already!
殺しは あくまで自分の快楽のために
やるのが楽しいんじゃん
Killing is only something I do for my own pleasure.
ラツ ド
Ladd...
俺はさぁ 叔父貢イ
Hey uncle, there's a special type of people I especially like to kill.
特に殺してやりたい種類の
連中がいるのよ
強いとガ弱いとか関係なくつてさぁ
Unrelated to whether they're strong or weak...
The ones I kill... The ones I have fun in killing...
俺が殺すのは…
殺して楽しいのはぁ…
緩みき つ た連中よ 分かる ?
Are those who feel completely safe.
Understand?
自分は絶対安全な場所にいて
Thinking they are in a completely safe place,
not thinking even in the least that they might die the next moment.
次の瞬間
自分が死ぬかもしれないってことを
これ一一つぽつちも者えてない
そういう奴よ
People like that.
ま つまり…
In other words, uncle... People like you!
今の叔父貴… あんたみたいな奴さ
やめてくれえ~~~つ
PLEASE STOP!
殺すわけないじゃんよ
弾なんて入ってないよ
There's no way I'll kill you.
Of course it was an empty gun.
叔父貴ィ 今まで
世話になつたんだもんよ
Uncle, I've been in your care up till now.
殺人鬼の俺でも
そんくらいの義理は通すぜ
Even a killing machine like me understands his debt to you.
Right?!
なあ
消えろ
Disappear...
I'll do that.
そ一すつかぁ 俺もそろそろ
着替えなくちゃいけねぇし
I have to change clothes soon as well.
How can you dress so happily?
どうして そんな
おめでたい格好をするんだ?
これから何十人も狭い列車の中で
殺すんだぜえ…
Soon I'll be killing countless people inside a narrow train.
白いほうが…
Don't you think it's cool to wear white? That way you can see the blood stains of the people I killed.
返り血が目立つて
力ッコいいじゃん?
うつ… うわ うわつ
へつへへ
ちよいち ちよっと待ってくれよ
このとおり 俺は丸腰だ
Wait, wait just a bit!
As you can see, I'm unarmed.
貢様…
You...
貴様ら何者だ?
Who are you guys?
怪しい者ですが
敵ではありませんよ
We might look suspicious, but we're not your enemies.
答えろ !
Answer me!
That's why...
だからぁ 俺はあんたらの
敵じやねえって!
We're not your enemy!
あがぐがが…
おっと…
ほい! ほれ!
Here, here.
くっ クノ
Dammit...
ちつ
Well then, it sure has become interesting! Interesting!
さぁて 面白くなってきましたねぇ
きやカヾりましたねぇつと
Making us into enemies... Don't think you'll be able to live through all this!
我々を敵にして
生き延ぴられると思うな!
The mafia guys I killed before, usually said something around those lines before I killed them.
俺が殺したマフイアとかもさぁ
たいてい死ぬ前に
そんなこと言つてたよ
ひつ…
グボオ‥
That's a pity!
残念でした
Easy, easy!
平気平気
Easier than Pete Herman!
ビ一卜ハ一マンよりは
全然弱いから !
Because you're way weaker!
You don't have any technique and power like Jack Johnson or Jack Dempsey either!
璽ヤック璽ヨンソンや
シヤツク丁ンプシ一みてスな!
パンチ力もテク二ツクもね工 !
お前 ボクサ一の名前 分かる?
You know any boxer names?
You know 'm, right?
分かるよなァ
アメリ力国民なら知ってて当然だ
If you're an American, of course you know!
If you say, you don't know, or something...
知らねえとか言つたら 許さねえ !
I won't forgive you!
I will NE-VER, forgive you!
絶対に ! 許しはしねえ
まあ 知つてても
許しやあ しねえんだけどなァ
And even if you know them,
I still, won't, forgive, you, though!
ぐはあ…
ぬおお…
Wow, you're still conscious!
ありゃあ? まだ意識があんだ?
やっぱ俺 パンチ力ねぇんだあ…
I really don't have much of a fist.
What do you want to do about that?!
なあ どうしてくれんだよ おい!
Hey!
There's no way the likes of you can block Sir Huey's path!
あんぐ やガら
貴様のような暗愚の輩に
ヒユ一イ師の道を…
ふさぐことがm できる ものか_
ぐおお ! おお…
俺はヒユ一イだの
お前らの正体だのには関心ねぇ
I have no interest in your identity, nor in Huey.
確かなのは
お前らが全員 敵だってこと
What's certain, is that all of you are our enemies.
お前らが わんさか武器を
持ってるってことだ
Because you guys are carrying loads of guns.
And above all!
そして何より
お前ら こう思つてるはずだ
With these hands...
You guys...
Are trash!
この列車で これだけすごい武器を
持ってる俺たちに逆らう奴なんていない
There can't be, anyone, on this train, who opposes us,
with weapons like the ones you have!
俺たちは最強だ
俺たちは安全だつてな!
Thinking "We are the strongest!"
Thinking "We are in a safe place!"
It sure must be fun. It sure must be fun!
楽しいだろうなぁ 楽しいだろうなあ
そんな奴らを殺すのは
Killing people like that,
dragging out your intestines,
腸を引きずり出すのは
ソ一セ一ジの中身みてえに
as if I was beating a sausage!
ぐつちゃぐちゃに すりつぶして
やるのはよおおおおおお…
Mashing it into oblivion!
It's dangerous!
Hey Ladd,
ラツ ドよう こり や一体
どうなつてんだ?
what's going on here?
マシンガンみてぇな音がしたから
来てみりゃよお
When we heard machine guns we came over to take a look but...
Give an explanation, Ladd.
説明しろよ ラツ ドよう
You must be Senator Beriam's wife, right?
べ ー丿 アム上院議員夫人だな ?
The order has changed.
順番が逆にな つ たぜ
あの黒服どもを全員始末したら
次は あんたの番だ
When I have taken care of all the people in the black suits,
it's your turn.
よろしくな
Nice to meet you.
Let's go men.
行くぞ お前ら
行くぞって こいつらどうすんだよ
"Let's go" you say?
What do we do with these people?
ほつとけ
Leave 'm.
Those people... I can use them.
Miss...
お嬢様 ダラス坊ちゃまさ
無事だけんばさ !
Young Mr. Dallas is surely all right.
そのうち ひよつこり
帰つていらつしゃいますよ
He'll come home some time eventually.
そうですね
You're right.
きつと… そうですよね…
Certainly...
You must be right.
あんまり いい気持ちはしないねぇ
Doesn't really make you feel good, does it?
知らない振りをするなんてのは…
Pretending not to know...
ウソをついているわけじゃない
It's not like we lied.
おおかた 分からないのは事実なんだ
It's true we don't know most of it.
Also fooled the people from Runorata into coming by later.
丿しノラ一夕の奴らにも
詳細は後巳にと ごまかしておいた
グス夕一ヴオは
ジ工ノア一ド家 当主の殺害をネ夕に
Apparently Gustavo is being blackmailed by Dallas with the news
ダラスにゆすられているということに
なつているそうだが
of the killing of the head of the Genoard family.
ありやウソだな
That must be a lie.
There must be a deeper lying reason for Baltro Runorata.
バ丿し卜ロ丿しノラ一夕には
裏の理由があるんだろう
それがなんなのか…
But what that is...
The Dallas case is top secret after all.
ダラスの件は
特秘事項だからねぇ…
特秘? ダラスはガン ド一ル兄弟が
始末したんじゃないのか?
Top secret?
Didn't the Gandor brothers take care of Dallas?
おっ と こいつはロがすベつたねえ
Oops, that was a slip of the tongue there.
What do you mean?
何だ? 同僚の俺にもしやベれないとは
どういうことだ?
Why can't you talk about it even to a colleague like me?
The director forbade me to talk about it as well...
う~ん 社長からも
ロ止めされてるんだよ
Wait, it can't be...
まさか あれか?
死なない連中にまつわることか?
Is it related to the people that can't die?
ごめん! 申し訳ない!
自分のロからは言えないよ!
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I can't tell you myself.
Please let me off the hook on this one.
どうか勘弁してほしい
許してくれ!
Forgive me.
Don't tell the Director I told you, okay?
あ~ 俺がロをすベらせたこと
社長には黙ってて ね!
おっと失礼…
Oh, my apologies.
おいおい 気をつけてくれよ
Hey, hey, watch where you walk.
Watch where you walk.
気をつけてくれよ
いいか 三リア
All right, Miria?
なあに アイザツク ?
What, Isaac?
ぜつつたい目立つような
マネはすんなよ
Don't do anything to stand out, okay?
I understand. If I just behave plainly, plainly, it's okay, right?
分かつてるよ
地味に地味に動けばいいんだね
そのとおりだ
分かつてるならいい
That's it exactly.
It's all right, if you know.
すげえなア どれに しよう !
It's really amazing! Which shall we pick?
How about one like this?
こんなのは?
こんなの勝手に売つていいのガ?
Is it alright to be selling stuff like this?
I wonder if this is a hat as well?
これも帽子なのかな ?
う一ん ちよ つ と奇抜すきるかな…
This one may be a little too eccentric...
強盗するには向かないかもね !
This one might not be suitable for robberies.
Old man, please calculate our change.
じい
爺さん 会計してくれ !
Okay, old man,
いいか 爺さん
俺たちが この店に来たってことは
きれいさつぱり忘れるんだなぁ !
forget that we were ever here!
忘れるんだなぁ !
Forget we were here!
If you should report us to the police...
もし警察なんかに通報したら…
えっ したら…
If you...
どうする?
What do we do?
ん一… 具体的に決まってないなら
殴るとかでいいんじゃない?
If we haven't decided concretely, beating him is fine, don't you think?
あっ そつか
I see.
So, old man, if you report us!
ともあれ爺さん ! 通報したら…
通報したら…
Report us!
ぶつ !
ぶつ!
We'll beat you!
Beat you!
それじや !
Well then!
おい
Hey!
ひつ
お釣 り
Your change.
こ ここここ 怖かつたあ
T-T-That was scary!
Scary!
怖かつ たあ
つゎもの
あの爺さん かなりの強者だぜ!
That old man was quite a person.
To be able to scare me so much with just one look.
たつた ひとにらみで俺をここまで
おぴえさせるとはな!
いや もちろん戦えば
勝てたけどよ ほら なんだ
Of course if we'd fought I would have won but...
三リアにケガでもあったら
大変だと思ってよ
I thought it'd be terrible if you got injured so...
Really?
ほんとうに?
Yea, of course!
ああ 本当さ!
強盗行脚を始めてから このー 年
Ever since we started robbing a year ago,
サンフランシスコから _
二ユ一ジヤ一ジ一まで87ケ所
from San Francisco to New Jersey, we've been to 87 places and seen lots of things!
色んな所を回つたけどよ
Has there ever been a time I exposed you to any danger?
俺が今までお前を危険な目に
遭わせたことがあるか?
87回くらい?
About 87 times?
それ見ろ
まだー00回以下じゃねぇか!
There look! It hasn't even been a hundred times yet!
That's true! Amazing!
ホン卜だ すつごお~い !
そうさ! この二ユ一ヨ一クで
最後の大仕事をして
That's what I mean!
We're gonna do our last big job here in New York,
あとはマイア三辺りで
のんぴり暮らすんだ
and after that we're gonna live leisurely in Miami!
After that the word danger will be foreign to us!
そうなりゃもう俺たちに
危険なんて言葉は無縁だぜ!
Foreign, right?!
無縁だね !
大きい家を買おう !
Let's buy a big house.
And create a pool there...
そこにプ一ルを作つて
朝から晩まで泳きつくそう
And swim from morning to evening!
But it's cold in the evening!
大丈夫 !
That's all right!
If we add ten stoves to that, the pool will heat up!
ス卜一ブをー0台くらいつけりや
プ一丿しも暖まるだろ!
Amazing, amazing!
すごおい すごおい!
アラブの王様だって
そんなにつけないよう !
Even Arab kings don't add that many to their pools!
それで庭には鉄道を走らせようぜ !
And let's put a railroad in our garden!
We can ride from our home to the gate by train each day!
家から門まで毎巳
汽車に揺られるのさ !
でも私たち そんなに
大金持ちになれるの?
But can we become that rich?
We can!
なれるさ ! 俺は三リアと一緒なら
大統領にだってなれる!
As long as I'm with you, I can even become the President!
Become king, become queen, we can even become jokers!
キングにだって クイ 一ンにだって
ジヨ一力一にだつてなれるさ!
よく分かんないけど すつ ごお~い !
I don't really understand, but it's amazing!
で その白服の連中は
一体何者だ?
And? Who are those white-clothed people?
We have no clue whatsoever.
皆目 見当がつきません
ともあれ 手の空いている人間を
一度 呼ぴ戻せ
Anyway, recall those who are still able to move for now.
Understood.
はい
Lまあ‥
これも試練と者えるベきか…
Do I have to think of this as a trial as well?
I don't think you can just dismiss it as such.
そう簡単に
たどり着けるとは思いませんよ
Don't you think so, Mr. Goose?
そうでしよ グ一ス殿
You're right.
そうだな…
ヒユ一イ師の高みへは通常の道では
たどり着けぬのだからな
You can't get to Sir Huey's height by taking normal roads.
Where are you going, Chane?
シヤ一ネ どこに行く?
いいんですか?
Is that okay?
放っておけ…
Leave her be.
あれは こなすべきことはこなす…
それに…
She pulls through when she has to.
Besides, she'll only live until tomorrow anyway.
どうせ明巳までの命だ
気をつけろ なぜ はねた
Watch out. Why did we hit them?
I'm sorry.
申し訳ございません
They suddenly danced out into the road.
突然 道に踊り出しまして
ブレ一キが間に合いませんでした
The brakes didn't make it.
What are you doing?!
That was cowardly!
痛いじやね一かよ
不意打ちは卑怯だぞ !
卑怯だぞ !
You listening' to us?!
It looks like they're alive...
生きているようだな…
ちゃんと聞いてんのか コラ
Yes, we weren't going that fast.
はい 速度が速度でしたから…
出せ
Step on it.
Understood.
はい
You running from us?!
Fight with us fair and square!
おい
おっ おい逃げる気か
セ一セ一ド一ド一と
シヨ一ブしろい~
Fight! Fight!
シヨ一フ シヨ一ブ
近頃の若い者は分からんな…
I really don't understand youngsters these days.
もつとも200年前から若い奴の
者えることなど 理解できなかったが…
I already couldn't understand youngsters' thoughts from 200 years ago but...
マイザ一…
あの若造が血迷った時から
Ever since Maiza lost his senses, I lost my faith in those younger than me.
私は年下の人間を
信用しなくなったのだ
セラ一ド様から見れば
From your point of view, the entire world is younger.
世界中の人間が年下になり ます
ふん…
で ラツ ドよお あの黒服ども
一体何なんだ?
So Ladd, who on earth are those people in the black suits?
They're a feast! It's amazing!
ごちそうさ! すげえベ?
ー人当たり 2 3人は殺せるんだぜ?
Everyone should be able to kill two or three.
しかも完全に
自分優位だと思つてるような
On top of that they're weaklings who think they have the upper hand!
ユルイ奴らをだ!
Well then.
さて‥ と
ここに群れてるのは
ヤバいから散るぜ
It's dangerous to gather round here, so we're gonna split up!
ル一アたちには俺が伝えとく
I'll tell Lua.
集合時間はテキ卜一 !
It's up to you when to assemble again.
When you think you've done enough come back here.
各自やってやつたぜ!と思つたら
ここに戻つてくること!
ヒヨオォォ イ工工工 オォオ
これはこれはク工一ツ様
Well, well, if it isn't Master Quates.
お久しゆうございます
It sure has been a while.
ふん…
たかが20年だ
そう久しくもない…
It's only been twenty years.
You can't call that a while.
Ohh, Master Quates!
おお ク工一ツ様
You look fine.
お元気そうで
You haven't changed a bit.
何一つ お変わりがない
バ一ンズとス夕一ジ工ンは
どうした?
Where are Barnes and Stagen?
Mr. Barnes is in the distillation room.
バ一ンズ様は蒸留所です
Mr. Stagen passed away last year.
ス夕一ジ工ン様は
昨年 おてくなりに…
そうか… 出来損ないの
未完成品では
I see.
I couldn't give you, failed incomplete products, eternal souls.
お前たちに永遠の魂まで
与えることはできなかった
ス夕一ジ工ンも
老衰では仕方がない…
Stagen was too old so it can't be helped.
あとー年ももてば 今巳の巳が
迎えられたものを…
If only he had lived for another year he would've been here today.
突発的な死の恐れが
なくなつたがゆえ
Because your fear for a sudden death disappeared,
老いに対する諸君の恐怖は
尋常ではなかつただろう
the anxiety towards aging you gentlemen felt, couldn't have been normal.
だが それも今日で終ゎる…
But all that ends today.
ついに完成品
完全なる大いなる万能薬 を
We finally succeeded in creating a finished product, a complete, great Cure-All Elixir.
作り出すことに
成功したのだからな!
完成品はバ一ンズの所か ?
The finished product is in Barnes' hands?
はい
Yes.
ノ_
工二ス 車でバ一ンズを迎スに付け
Ennis, go and pick Barnes up with the car.
はい
Understood.
工二ス
Ennis...
はい
Yes?
もし完成品に
手を出していたら…
If he has touched the product, no need to hesitate, kill him.
構うことはない 殺せ
保存にしくじって
薬をダメにしていた場合も 殺せ
If he failed to preserve the medicine and it has become useless, kill him too.
承知しました
Understood.
3ーー
ぐはあ…
人の足にケリ入れといて
そのまま行くつもりかあ ジジイ
You kick someone's leg, and you wanted to go just like that, old man?
足を引つかけてきたのは
貴様らのほう…
You're the ones that tripped on me!
へへへ うせろ クズどもがつて
結構なこと言ってくれたのは
"Leave scum!" you were the one who said stuff like that, weren't you?
てめえのほうだろうがよ !
おかげで ついつい足が
出ちまつ たんだろ ?
Thanks to that I accidentally stuck my leg out!
You were the one walking into it!
勝手に引つかかったのは
てめえだろうが!
ぐゎツ !
ゎ 分かつた 私が悪かつた
I understand!
It was my bad!
I-If you want money, I'll give it to you!
か か 金 金ならやる
I didn't ask for your opinion!
てめえの意見は聞いてねえ
Huh? Is that liquor?
ああ ? 酒か?
ううつ!
What's the matter, old man?
何だ ジジイ その箱は
そんなに大事なもんか?
Is that box really that precious to you?
バ一ンズさん…
Mr. Barnes...
失礼…
Excuse me.
大丈夫ですか ?
Are you all right?
Ah, yes.
申し訳あ り ませんでした
I'm very sorry.
I'm looking for someone so...
私 人を捜しているので これで…
おい あんた!
Hey! You!
Wait up!
待てよ !
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Jacuzzi Splot Cries, Gets Scared
and Musters Reckless Valor
Jacuzzi is amazing!
Why, Isaac?
I mean, he cries, and is scared yet he shows his courage recklessly!
By banyuu (universal), you mean inryoku (gravitation) right?
That's right, Miria!
I mean he cries and is scared, yet he throws gravitation around!
Jacuzzi is amazing!
Banyuu can mean both "reckless courage" (蛮勇) and "universal" (万有) depending on which characters you use. The characters used in the title mean "reckless courage", however Miria and Isaac misunderstand and think "universal" is meant. Since "banyuu inryoku" means "universal gravitation" they think it's that banyuu.